[{"answer": " Hi, Amy.  Im Stacey, one of the International student advisors at the university", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Hi Stacey.  Nice to meet you.  I have a friend in Mexico that wants to come stud", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Hi, Amy.  Im Stacey, one of the International student advisors at the university", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " OK.  First of all, let me ask you some questions about her situation.  Does sh", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Hi Stacey.  Nice to meet you.  I have a friend in Mexico that wants to come stud", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " She wants to come and get a Bachelors degree", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 27, "question": " OK.  First of all, let me ask you some questions about her situation.  Does sh", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " OK.  And would her government or another organization fund her", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 28, "question": " She wants to come and get a Bachelors degree", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 29, "question": " OK.  And would her government or another organization fund her", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Would the government of Mexico or another organization be paying for he", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 33, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Oh, no.  Shell be paying herself", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Would the government of Mexico or another organization be paying for he", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " All right.  It sounds like shell want to come to the U.S. on an F-1 student visa", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Oh, no.  Shell be paying herself", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " F-1?  OK.  How does she do that", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 39, "question": " All right.  It sounds like shell want to come to the U.S. on an F-1 student visa", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " First of all, she has to apply and get accepted to a department at the university", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 40, "question": " F-1?  OK.  How does she do that", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " What are the requirements for admission", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 41, "question": " First of all, she has to apply and get accepted to a department at the university", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Youll have to talk to the Admissions department for that info", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 42, "question": " What are the requirements for admission", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Youll have to talk to the Admissions department for that info", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Once shes admitted, the school will issue her a form I-20, which is one of th", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 44, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Do you give her the visa too", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Once shes admitted, the school will issue her a form I-20, which is one of th", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " No, once she has her I-20, she needs to make an appointment with the U.S", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Do you give her the visa too", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Mmmmhmmm", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 54, "question": " No, once she has her I-20, she needs to make an appointment with the U.S", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " For the appointment, shell need her acceptance letter to the school, her I-20", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Mmmmhmmm", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " What do you mean by financial documentation and proof of ties to her hom", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 59, "question": " For the appointment, shell need her acceptance letter to the school, her I-20", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Well, shell need to show financial information to the officer at the embassy tha", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 63, "question": " What do you mean by financial documentation and proof of ties to her hom", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " OK, she could bring her bank statements", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Well, shell need to show financial information to the officer at the embassy tha", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " That would work.  Now, the F-1 visa is a non-immigrant visa, which means tha", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 69, "question": " OK, she could bring her bank statements", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Is that important to show", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 77, "question": " That would work.  Now, the F-1 visa is a non-immigrant visa, which means tha", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Yes it is.  Not providing proof of this could result in denial of the visa", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Is that important to show", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " If her visa is denied can she still come with just her I-20", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Yes it is.  Not providing proof of this could result in denial of the visa", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " No, shell need an I-20 and an F-1 visa to enter the U.S. as a student", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 80, "question": " If her visa is denied can she still come with just her I-20", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " OK.  If she does come here as a student are there any special rules for her as a", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 81, "question": " No, shell need an I-20 and an F-1 visa to enter the U.S. as a student", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Yes, there are.  Shell have to take a minimum of 12 credits each term, she ca", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 85, "question": " OK.  If she does come here as a student are there any special rules for her as a", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " I see.  So she cant just come here and do whatever she wants like a domesti", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Yes, there are.  Shell have to take a minimum of 12 credits each term, she ca", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " No, unfortunately, international students have a lot more to think about an", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 95, "question": " I see.  So she cant just come here and do whatever she wants like a domesti", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " I see.  Well, Ill tell my friend about the information you told me today.  It will b", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 99, "question": " No, unfortunately, international students have a lot more to think about an", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  If she has any other questions, she can take a look at ou", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 103, "question": " I see.  Well, Ill tell my friend about the information you told me today.  It will b", "qSentId": 102},{"answer": " OK.  Thank you.  Bye", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 107, "question": " Youre welcome.  If she has any other questions, she can take a look at ou", "qSentId": 106},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "04-06", "aSentId": 108, "question": " OK.  Thank you.  Bye", "qSentId": 107}]
